{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, J, C, V and directed edges J->C, J->V, C->V, Z->J, Z->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83640066", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node Z and node V .", "answer": "[{'J', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, J, C, V and directed edges J->C, J->V, C->V, Z->J, Z->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83640066", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node Z and node V .", "answer": "{'J', 'C'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, J, C, V and directed edges J->C, J->V, C->V, Z->J, Z->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83640066", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node Z and node V d-separated by nodeset set()?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, J, C, V and directed edges J->C, J->V, C->V, Z->J, Z->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83640066", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node Z and node V?\nA. {'J'}\nB. {'J', 'C'}\nC. {'C'}\nD. set()", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, Z, P, V and directed edges C->V, P->V, C->Z, Z->P, Z->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57227207", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node P and node C .", "answer": "[{'Z'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, Z, P, V and directed edges C->V, P->V, C->Z, Z->P, Z->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57227207", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node P and node C .", "answer": "{'Z'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, Z, P, V and directed edges C->V, P->V, C->Z, Z->P, Z->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57227207", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node C and node P d-separated by nodeset set()?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes C, Z, P, V and directed edges C->V, P->V, C->Z, Z->P, Z->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57227207", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node C and node P?\nA. {'Z', 'V'}\nB. {'V'}\nC. {'Z'}\nD. set()", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, N, Z, C and directed edges Z->C, N->Z, F->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87467573", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node C and node N .", "answer": "[{'Z'}, {'F', 'Z'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, N, Z, C and directed edges Z->C, N->Z, F->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87467573", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node C and node N .", "answer": "{'Z'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, N, Z, C and directed edges Z->C, N->Z, F->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87467573", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node F and node N d-separated by nodeset set()?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, N, Z, C and directed edges Z->C, N->Z, F->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "87467573", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node N and node F?\nA. set()\nB. {'C'}\nC. {'Z'}\nD. {'Z', 'C'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, J, S and directed edges M->J, E->S, M->E, J->S, M->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95005213", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node E and node J .", "answer": "[{'M'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, J, S and directed edges M->J, E->S, M->E, J->S, M->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95005213", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node E and node J .", "answer": "{'M'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, J, S and directed edges M->J, E->S, M->E, J->S, M->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95005213", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node J and node E d-separated by nodeset {'S', 'M'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, E, J, S and directed edges M->J, E->S, M->E, J->S, M->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95005213", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node E and node J?\nA. {'S', 'M'}\nB. set()\nC. {'S'}\nD. {'M'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, L, I, G and directed edges M->L, M->G, L->G, L->I, I->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17537353", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node I and node M .", "answer": "[{'L'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, L, I, G and directed edges M->L, M->G, L->G, L->I, I->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17537353", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node I and node M .", "answer": "{'L'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, L, I, G and directed edges M->L, M->G, L->G, L->I, I->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17537353", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node I and node M d-separated by nodeset {'G', 'L'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, L, I, G and directed edges M->L, M->G, L->G, L->I, I->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17537353", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node M and node I?\nA. {'G'}\nB. set()\nC. {'G', 'L'}\nD. {'L'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, Y, T, Q, U and directed edges Y->Q, T->U, M->U, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "93435805", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node T and node M .", "answer": "[set(), {'Q'}, {'Y'}, {'Q', 'Y'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, Y, T, Q, U and directed edges Y->Q, T->U, M->U, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "93435805", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node T and node M .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, Y, T, Q, U and directed edges Y->Q, T->U, M->U, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "93435805", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node M and node Y d-separated by nodeset {'U', 'T'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, Y, T, Q, U and directed edges Y->Q, T->U, M->U, M->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "93435805", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node T and node M?\nA. {'U', 'Y', 'Q'}\nB. {'U', 'Q'}\nC. set()\nD. {'U'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, F, U, A, V and directed edges F->V, O->F, O->U, F->U, U->A, O->A, U->V, F->A.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95388106", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node A and node V .", "answer": "[{'F', 'U'}, {'F', 'U', 'O'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, F, U, A, V and directed edges F->V, O->F, O->U, F->U, U->A, O->A, U->V, F->A.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95388106", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node A and node V .", "answer": "{'F', 'U'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, F, U, A, V and directed edges F->V, O->F, O->U, F->U, U->A, O->A, U->V, F->A.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95388106", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node V and node O d-separated by nodeset {'F', 'U'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, F, U, A, V and directed edges F->V, O->F, O->U, F->U, U->A, O->A, U->V, F->A.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "95388106", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node V and node A?\nA. {'F'}\nB. {'F', 'U', 'O'}\nC. {'O'}\nD. {'F', 'O'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, P, C, M and directed edges P->C, N->C, N->P, X->C, P->M, N->X, X->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08821198", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node C and node M .", "answer": "[{'P', 'X'}, {'P', 'X', 'N'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, P, C, M and directed edges P->C, N->C, N->P, X->C, P->M, N->X, X->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08821198", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node C and node M .", "answer": "{'P', 'X'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, P, C, M and directed edges P->C, N->C, N->P, X->C, P->M, N->X, X->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08821198", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node X and node P d-separated by nodeset {'N'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes N, X, P, C, M and directed edges P->C, N->C, N->P, X->C, P->M, N->X, X->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "08821198", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node M and node N?\nA. {'P', 'C', 'X'}\nB. set()\nC. {'X'}\nD. {'C', 'X'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, O, R, F, C and directed edges I->C, R->C, R->F, F->C, O->F, I->O, I->R, O->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "03374785", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node F and node I .", "answer": "[{'R', 'O'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, O, R, F, C and directed edges I->C, R->C, R->F, F->C, O->F, I->O, I->R, O->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "03374785", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node F and node I .", "answer": "{'R', 'O'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, O, R, F, C and directed edges I->C, R->C, R->F, F->C, O->F, I->O, I->R, O->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "03374785", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node F and node I d-separated by nodeset {'C', 'O'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, O, R, F, C and directed edges I->C, R->C, R->F, F->C, O->F, I->O, I->R, O->C.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "03374785", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node O and node R?\nA. {'F'}\nB. set()\nC. {'F', 'C'}\nD. {'I'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, T, Z, K, O and directed edges X->O, Z->K, T->Z, X->T, X->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "21648824", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node O and node T .", "answer": "[{'X'}, {'Z', 'X'}, {'K', 'X'}, {'Z', 'K', 'X'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, T, Z, K, O and directed edges X->O, Z->K, T->Z, X->T, X->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "21648824", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node O and node T .", "answer": "{'X'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, T, Z, K, O and directed edges X->O, Z->K, T->Z, X->T, X->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "21648824", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node Z and node O d-separated by nodeset set()?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, T, Z, K, O and directed edges X->O, Z->K, T->Z, X->T, X->Z.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "21648824", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node X and node K?\nA. {'O'}\nB. {'T'}\nC. {'Z', 'T'}\nD. {'T', 'O'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, N, Q, U, X, E and directed edges H->Q, H->X, H->E, Q->U, H->U, Q->E, U->X, N->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48833954", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node N and node E .", "answer": "[{'H', 'Q'}, {'H', 'U', 'Q'}, {'H', 'X', 'Q'}, {'H', 'U', 'X', 'Q'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, N, Q, U, X, E and directed edges H->Q, H->X, H->E, Q->U, H->U, Q->E, U->X, N->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48833954", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node N and node E .", "answer": "{'H', 'Q'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, N, Q, U, X, E and directed edges H->Q, H->X, H->E, Q->U, H->U, Q->E, U->X, N->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48833954", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node N and node E d-separated by nodeset {'H', 'Q'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, N, Q, U, X, E and directed edges H->Q, H->X, H->E, Q->U, H->U, Q->E, U->X, N->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "48833954", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node N and node E?\nA. set()\nB. {'H'}\nC. {'Q'}\nD. {'H', 'U', 'Q'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, C, U, W, J, N and directed edges U->N, C->N, B->U, U->J, W->N, J->N, B->W, B->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "42655914", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node J and node W .", "answer": "[{'B'}, {'B', 'U'}, {'B', 'C'}, {'B', 'U', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, C, U, W, J, N and directed edges U->N, C->N, B->U, U->J, W->N, J->N, B->W, B->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "42655914", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node J and node W .", "answer": "{'B'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, C, U, W, J, N and directed edges U->N, C->N, B->U, U->J, W->N, J->N, B->W, B->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "42655914", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node J and node W d-separated by nodeset {'B', 'U', 'C'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, C, U, W, J, N and directed edges U->N, C->N, B->U, U->J, W->N, J->N, B->W, B->J.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "42655914", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node C and node B?\nA. {'U', 'W', 'J', 'N'}\nB. {'U', 'N'}\nC. {'U', 'W', 'N'}\nD. {'N'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, U, X, D, E, H and directed edges L->X, L->D, L->H, D->E, L->U, X->E, X->H, X->D, E->H.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57048334", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node D and node H .", "answer": "[{'E', 'L', 'X'}, {'U', 'E', 'L', 'X'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, U, X, D, E, H and directed edges L->X, L->D, L->H, D->E, L->U, X->E, X->H, X->D, E->H.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57048334", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node D and node H .", "answer": "{'E', 'L', 'X'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, U, X, D, E, H and directed edges L->X, L->D, L->H, D->E, L->U, X->E, X->H, X->D, E->H.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57048334", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node U and node X d-separated by nodeset {'H', 'L', 'D'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, U, X, D, E, H and directed edges L->X, L->D, L->H, D->E, L->U, X->E, X->H, X->D, E->H.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "57048334", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node H and node U?\nA. {'D', 'E', 'X'}\nB. {'D', 'E'}\nC. set()\nD. {'E', 'L', 'X'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, B, O, D, Z, L and directed edges D->Z, M->L, O->Z, O->D, B->O, M->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83013848", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node B and node Z .", "answer": "[{'O'}, {'D', 'O'}, {'M', 'O'}, {'L', 'O'}, {'D', 'M', 'O'}, {'D', 'L', 'O'}, {'M', 'L', 'O'}, {'D', 'M', 'L', 'O'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, B, O, D, Z, L and directed edges D->Z, M->L, O->Z, O->D, B->O, M->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83013848", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node B and node Z .", "answer": "{'O'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, B, O, D, Z, L and directed edges D->Z, M->L, O->Z, O->D, B->O, M->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83013848", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node D and node B d-separated by nodeset {'M', 'L', 'O'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, B, O, D, Z, L and directed edges D->Z, M->L, O->Z, O->D, B->O, M->O.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "83013848", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node M and node D?\nA. {'Z', 'L'}\nB. {'L'}\nC. set()\nD. {'O'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, D, K, Y, L, G and directed edges K->G, L->G, D->Y, Y->G, K->L, F->G, D->K, F->Y, D->G, Y->L.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "90880097", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node F and node D .", "answer": "[set(), {'K'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, D, K, Y, L, G and directed edges K->G, L->G, D->Y, Y->G, K->L, F->G, D->K, F->Y, D->G, Y->L.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "90880097", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node F and node D .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, D, K, Y, L, G and directed edges K->G, L->G, D->Y, Y->G, K->L, F->G, D->K, F->Y, D->G, Y->L.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "90880097", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node F and node K d-separated by nodeset {'Y'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes F, D, K, Y, L, G and directed edges K->G, L->G, D->Y, Y->G, K->L, F->G, D->K, F->Y, D->G, Y->L.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "90880097", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node L and node D?\nA. {'F', 'Y', 'K'}\nB. {'F', 'G', 'Y'}\nC. set()\nD. {'F', 'Y'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, P, N, S, W, B, E and directed edges K->E, S->B, S->E, P->E, N->E, K->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07851764", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node E and node B .", "answer": "[{'S'}, {'S', 'W'}, {'S', 'K'}, {'S', 'P'}, {'S', 'N'}, {'S', 'W', 'K'}, {'S', 'P', 'W'}, {'S', 'W', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'K'}, {'S', 'K', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'W', 'K'}, {'S', 'W', 'K', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'W', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'K', 'N'}, {'S', 'W', 'K', 'P', 'N'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, P, N, S, W, B, E and directed edges K->E, S->B, S->E, P->E, N->E, K->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07851764", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node E and node B .", "answer": "{'S'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, P, N, S, W, B, E and directed edges K->E, S->B, S->E, P->E, N->E, K->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07851764", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node N and node P d-separated by nodeset {'S', 'W', 'K', 'B', 'E'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, P, N, S, W, B, E and directed edges K->E, S->B, S->E, P->E, N->E, K->W.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07851764", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node B and node W?\nA. {'S', 'N'}\nB. {'P', 'E'}\nC. {'E', 'N'}\nD. {'E'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes T, C, I, M, J, N, E and directed edges C->E, C->M, C->J, M->J, T->J, M->N, I->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37212262", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node N and node T .", "answer": "[set(), {'E'}, {'M'}, {'I'}, {'C'}, {'M', 'E'}, {'I', 'E'}, {'E', 'C'}, {'M', 'J'}, {'I', 'M'}, {'M', 'C'}, {'I', 'C'}, {'M', 'E', 'J'}, {'I', 'M', 'E'}, {'M', 'E', 'C'}, {'I', 'E', 'C'}, {'I', 'M', 'J'}, {'M', 'J', 'C'}, {'I', 'M', 'C'}, {'I', 'M', 'E', 'J'}, {'M', 'E', 'J', 'C'}, {'I', 'M', 'E', 'C'}, {'I', 'M', 'J', 'C'}, {'E', 'J', 'M', 'I', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes T, C, I, M, J, N, E and directed edges C->E, C->M, C->J, M->J, T->J, M->N, I->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37212262", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node N and node T .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes T, C, I, M, J, N, E and directed edges C->E, C->M, C->J, M->J, T->J, M->N, I->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37212262", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node T and node E d-separated by nodeset {'I', 'M', 'J', 'N'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes T, C, I, M, J, N, E and directed edges C->E, C->M, C->J, M->J, T->J, M->N, I->M.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "37212262", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node C and node N?\nA. {'I'}\nB. {'T'}\nC. {'M', 'E', 'J'}\nD. {'I', 'T'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, M, T, Q, Y, P, E and directed edges M->Q, P->E, Y->E, V->M, V->E, T->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "26112983", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node V and node P .", "answer": "[set(), {'Q'}, {'Y'}, {'M'}, {'T'}, {'Q', 'Y'}, {'Q', 'M'}, {'Q', 'T'}, {'M', 'Y'}, {'T', 'Y'}, {'M', 'T'}, {'Q', 'M', 'Y'}, {'Q', 'T', 'Y'}, {'Q', 'M', 'T'}, {'M', 'T', 'Y'}, {'Q', 'M', 'T', 'Y'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, M, T, Q, Y, P, E and directed edges M->Q, P->E, Y->E, V->M, V->E, T->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "26112983", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node V and node P .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, M, T, Q, Y, P, E and directed edges M->Q, P->E, Y->E, V->M, V->E, T->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "26112983", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node P and node Q d-separated by nodeset {'E', 'T', 'V'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, M, T, Q, Y, P, E and directed edges M->Q, P->E, Y->E, V->M, V->E, T->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "26112983", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node Q and node Y?\nA. {'T', 'P', 'E'}\nB. {'M', 'P', 'V'}\nC. {'E'}\nD. {'E', 'T'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, L, I, D, B, O, Y and directed edges D->Y, I->Y, L->Y, L->O, Z->B, Z->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "69378012", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node L and node Z .", "answer": "[set(), {'B'}, {'D'}, {'O'}, {'I'}, {'B', 'D'}, {'B', 'O'}, {'B', 'I'}, {'D', 'Y'}, {'D', 'O'}, {'D', 'I'}, {'I', 'O'}, {'B', 'D', 'Y'}, {'B', 'D', 'O'}, {'B', 'D', 'I'}, {'B', 'I', 'O'}, {'D', 'Y', 'O'}, {'D', 'I', 'Y'}, {'D', 'I', 'O'}, {'B', 'D', 'Y', 'O'}, {'B', 'D', 'I', 'Y'}, {'B', 'D', 'I', 'O'}, {'D', 'I', 'Y', 'O'}, {'B', 'D', 'Y', 'O', 'I'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, L, I, D, B, O, Y and directed edges D->Y, I->Y, L->Y, L->O, Z->B, Z->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "69378012", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node L and node Z .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, L, I, D, B, O, Y and directed edges D->Y, I->Y, L->Y, L->O, Z->B, Z->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "69378012", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node Z and node I d-separated by nodeset {'B', 'Y'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Z, L, I, D, B, O, Y and directed edges D->Y, I->Y, L->Y, L->O, Z->B, Z->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "69378012", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node B and node Y?\nA. {'O'}\nB. {'I', 'L'}\nC. {'I', 'L', 'O'}\nD. {'Z', 'D', 'L', 'O'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, C, D, B, V, F, W and directed edges D->W, C->W, B->F, B->V, O->W, C->B, O->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94399700", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node D and node B .", "answer": "[set(), {'F'}, {'V'}, {'O'}, {'C'}, {'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'V'}, {'F', 'O'}, {'F', 'C'}, {'V', 'O'}, {'V', 'C'}, {'C', 'O'}, {'F', 'W', 'C'}, {'W', 'C', 'O'}, {'F', 'V', 'O'}, {'F', 'V', 'C'}, {'F', 'C', 'O'}, {'V', 'C', 'O'}, {'F', 'W', 'C', 'O'}, {'O', 'W', 'C', 'V'}, {'F', 'V', 'C', 'O'}, {'W', 'F', 'V', 'O', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, C, D, B, V, F, W and directed edges D->W, C->W, B->F, B->V, O->W, C->B, O->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94399700", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node D and node B .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, C, D, B, V, F, W and directed edges D->W, C->W, B->F, B->V, O->W, C->B, O->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94399700", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node F and node V d-separated by nodeset {'B', 'W', 'C', 'O'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes O, C, D, B, V, F, W and directed edges D->W, C->W, B->F, B->V, O->W, C->B, O->V.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "94399700", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node D and node O?\nA. {'F', 'W'}\nB. {'W', 'C'}\nC. {'B', 'V', 'C'}\nD. {'W', 'C', 'V'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, K, C, Y, B, R, L, W and directed edges K->C, R->L, B->L, B->W, J->K, B->R, C->Y, K->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "55821370", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node Y and node B .", "answer": "[{'K'}, {'C'}, {'W', 'K'}, {'W', 'C'}, {'R', 'K'}, {'J', 'K'}, {'L', 'K'}, {'C', 'K'}, {'R', 'C'}, {'J', 'C'}, {'C', 'L'}, {'R', 'W', 'K'}, {'W', 'J', 'K'}, {'L', 'W', 'K'}, {'W', 'C', 'K'}, {'R', 'W', 'C'}, {'W', 'J', 'C'}, {'W', 'C', 'L'}, {'R', 'J', 'K'}, {'L', 'R', 'K'}, {'R', 'C', 'K'}, {'L', 'J', 'K'}, {'C', 'J', 'K'}, {'L', 'C', 'K'}, {'R', 'J', 'C'}, {'R', 'C', 'L'}, {'C', 'J', 'L'}, {'R', 'W', 'J', 'K'}, {'L', 'R', 'W', 'K'}, {'R', 'W', 'C', 'K'}, {'L', 'W', 'J', 'K'}, {'C', 'W', 'J', 'K'}, {'L', 'W', 'C', 'K'}, {'R', 'W', 'J', 'C'}, {'R', 'W', 'C', 'L'}, {'C', 'W', 'J', 'L'}, {'L', 'R', 'J', 'K'}, {'C', 'R', 'J', 'K'}, {'L', 'R', 'C', 'K'}, {'C', 'L', 'J', 'K'}, {'C', 'R', 'J', 'L'}, {'W', 'K', 'R', 'J', 'L'}, {'W', 'K', 'R', 'J', 'C'}, {'W', 'K', 'R', 'L', 'C'}, {'W', 'K', 'J', 'L', 'C'}, {'W', 'R', 'J', 'L', 'C'}, {'K', 'R', 'J', 'L', 'C'}, {'W', 'K', 'R', 'J', 'L', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, K, C, Y, B, R, L, W and directed edges K->C, R->L, B->L, B->W, J->K, B->R, C->Y, K->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "55821370", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node Y and node B .", "answer": "{'K'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, K, C, Y, B, R, L, W and directed edges K->C, R->L, B->L, B->W, J->K, B->R, C->Y, K->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "55821370", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node W and node K d-separated by nodeset {'B', 'C', 'Y', 'L'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, K, C, Y, B, R, L, W and directed edges K->C, R->L, B->L, B->W, J->K, B->R, C->Y, K->B.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "55821370", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node K and node Y?\nA. {'R'}\nB. {'R', 'L'}\nC. {'C', 'J', 'L'}\nD. {'R', 'W', 'J', 'L'}", "answer": "C", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, B, J, T, E, A, G, C and directed edges J->G, G->C, T->A, B->C, T->G, U->G, E->A, B->J, J->T, E->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17852028", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node U and node B .", "answer": "[set(), {'A'}, {'E'}, {'J'}, {'T'}, {'G', 'J'}, {'E', 'A'}, {'A', 'J'}, {'T', 'A'}, {'E', 'J'}, {'E', 'T'}, {'T', 'J'}, {'G', 'A', 'J'}, {'G', 'E', 'J'}, {'G', 'T', 'J'}, {'G', 'J', 'C'}, {'E', 'A', 'J'}, {'T', 'E', 'A'}, {'T', 'A', 'J'}, {'T', 'E', 'J'}, {'G', 'E', 'A', 'J'}, {'G', 'T', 'A', 'J'}, {'C', 'G', 'A', 'J'}, {'T', 'G', 'E', 'J'}, {'G', 'E', 'J', 'C'}, {'G', 'T', 'J', 'C'}, {'T', 'E', 'A', 'J'}, {'G', 'A', 'E', 'J', 'T'}, {'G', 'A', 'E', 'J', 'C'}, {'G', 'A', 'T', 'J', 'C'}, {'G', 'E', 'J', 'T', 'C'}, {'G', 'A', 'E', 'J', 'T', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, B, J, T, E, A, G, C and directed edges J->G, G->C, T->A, B->C, T->G, U->G, E->A, B->J, J->T, E->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17852028", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node U and node B .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, B, J, T, E, A, G, C and directed edges J->G, G->C, T->A, B->C, T->G, U->G, E->A, B->J, J->T, E->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17852028", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node B and node G d-separated by nodeset {'U', 'T', 'E', 'A'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, B, J, T, E, A, G, C and directed edges J->G, G->C, T->A, B->C, T->G, U->G, E->A, B->J, J->T, E->G.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "17852028", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node U and node E?\nA. {'B', 'J', 'C'}\nB. {'G', 'A', 'B', 'J', 'T', 'C'}\nC. {'G', 'T', 'J'}\nD. {'T'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, Z, U, R, Q, N, W, O and directed edges R->N, K->R, W->O, K->O, Z->U, R->O, N->W, U->R, U->O, U->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07908429", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node Z and node O .", "answer": "[{'U'}, {'U', 'Q'}, {'U', 'W'}, {'U', 'K'}, {'U', 'R'}, {'U', 'N'}, {'U', 'Q', 'W'}, {'U', 'Q', 'K'}, {'U', 'Q', 'R'}, {'U', 'Q', 'N'}, {'U', 'W', 'K'}, {'U', 'R', 'W'}, {'U', 'W', 'N'}, {'U', 'R', 'K'}, {'U', 'K', 'N'}, {'U', 'R', 'N'}, {'U', 'Q', 'W', 'K'}, {'U', 'Q', 'R', 'W'}, {'U', 'Q', 'W', 'N'}, {'U', 'Q', 'R', 'K'}, {'U', 'Q', 'K', 'N'}, {'U', 'Q', 'R', 'N'}, {'U', 'R', 'W', 'K'}, {'U', 'W', 'K', 'N'}, {'U', 'R', 'W', 'N'}, {'U', 'R', 'K', 'N'}, {'Q', 'W', 'K', 'R', 'U'}, {'Q', 'W', 'K', 'U', 'N'}, {'Q', 'W', 'R', 'U', 'N'}, {'Q', 'K', 'R', 'U', 'N'}, {'W', 'K', 'R', 'U', 'N'}, {'Q', 'W', 'K', 'R', 'U', 'N'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, Z, U, R, Q, N, W, O and directed edges R->N, K->R, W->O, K->O, Z->U, R->O, N->W, U->R, U->O, U->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07908429", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node Z and node O .", "answer": "{'U'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, Z, U, R, Q, N, W, O and directed edges R->N, K->R, W->O, K->O, Z->U, R->O, N->W, U->R, U->O, U->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07908429", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node K and node Z d-separated by nodeset {'U'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, Z, U, R, Q, N, W, O and directed edges R->N, K->R, W->O, K->O, Z->U, R->O, N->W, U->R, U->O, U->Q.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "07908429", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node W and node Q?\nA. {'R', 'O'}\nB. {'Z', 'U', 'K', 'N'}\nC. {'O', 'R', 'K', 'N'}\nD. {'Z', 'R', 'O'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, H, J, T, O, P, N, Q and directed edges O->Q, J->N, H->O, A->H, A->J, P->N, O->N, T->N, A->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40302845", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node T and node P .", "answer": "[set(), {'Q'}, {'A'}, {'J'}, {'O'}, {'H'}, {'Q', 'A'}, {'Q', 'J'}, {'Q', 'O'}, {'H', 'Q'}, {'A', 'J'}, {'A', 'O'}, {'H', 'A'}, {'J', 'O'}, {'H', 'J'}, {'H', 'O'}, {'Q', 'A', 'J'}, {'Q', 'A', 'O'}, {'H', 'Q', 'A'}, {'Q', 'J', 'O'}, {'H', 'Q', 'J'}, {'H', 'Q', 'O'}, {'A', 'J', 'O'}, {'H', 'A', 'J'}, {'H', 'A', 'O'}, {'H', 'J', 'O'}, {'Q', 'A', 'J', 'O'}, {'H', 'Q', 'A', 'J'}, {'H', 'Q', 'A', 'O'}, {'H', 'Q', 'J', 'O'}, {'H', 'A', 'J', 'O'}, {'Q', 'A', 'J', 'H', 'O'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, H, J, T, O, P, N, Q and directed edges O->Q, J->N, H->O, A->H, A->J, P->N, O->N, T->N, A->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40302845", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node T and node P .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, H, J, T, O, P, N, Q and directed edges O->Q, J->N, H->O, A->H, A->J, P->N, O->N, T->N, A->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40302845", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node P and node J d-separated by nodeset {'Q', 'N', 'A', 'H', 'O'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes A, H, J, T, O, P, N, Q and directed edges O->Q, J->N, H->O, A->H, A->J, P->N, O->N, T->N, A->T.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "40302845", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node O and node P?\nA. {'H', 'N'}\nB. {'H', 'A', 'J', 'N'}\nC. {'Q', 'A', 'J', 'H', 'N', 'T'}\nD. {'H', 'Q', 'T', 'J'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Q, O, U, M, W, V, D, G and directed edges U->M, O->G, Q->G, Q->U, U->G, Q->W, U->W, W->V, M->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25274121", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node Q and node O .", "answer": "[set(), {'W'}, {'D'}, {'V'}, {'U'}, {'M'}, {'D', 'W'}, {'W', 'V'}, {'U', 'W'}, {'M', 'W'}, {'D', 'V'}, {'U', 'D'}, {'D', 'M'}, {'U', 'V'}, {'M', 'V'}, {'U', 'M'}, {'D', 'W', 'V'}, {'U', 'D', 'W'}, {'D', 'M', 'W'}, {'U', 'W', 'V'}, {'M', 'W', 'V'}, {'U', 'M', 'W'}, {'U', 'D', 'V'}, {'D', 'M', 'V'}, {'U', 'D', 'M'}, {'U', 'M', 'V'}, {'U', 'D', 'W', 'V'}, {'D', 'M', 'W', 'V'}, {'U', 'D', 'M', 'W'}, {'U', 'M', 'W', 'V'}, {'U', 'D', 'M', 'V'}, {'W', 'D', 'V', 'U', 'M'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Q, O, U, M, W, V, D, G and directed edges U->M, O->G, Q->G, Q->U, U->G, Q->W, U->W, W->V, M->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25274121", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node Q and node O .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Q, O, U, M, W, V, D, G and directed edges U->M, O->G, Q->G, Q->U, U->G, Q->W, U->W, W->V, M->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25274121", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node D and node V d-separated by nodeset {'Q', 'O'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Q, O, U, M, W, V, D, G and directed edges U->M, O->G, Q->G, Q->U, U->G, Q->W, U->W, W->V, M->D.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "25274121", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node Q and node V?\nA. {'D', 'W', 'O'}\nB. {'U', 'D', 'G', 'M'}\nC. {'U', 'D', 'G', 'O'}\nD. {'D', 'G', 'M'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, C, N, U, W, G, K, Z, F and directed edges W->G, N->F, W->K, R->U, N->G, U->F, R->N, G->Z, C->Z, R->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22129727", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node K and node N .", "answer": "[set(), {'W'}, {'F'}, {'R'}, {'U'}, {'C'}, {'Z', 'W'}, {'G', 'W'}, {'F', 'W'}, {'R', 'W'}, {'U', 'W'}, {'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'R'}, {'F', 'U'}, {'F', 'C'}, {'U', 'R'}, {'R', 'C'}, {'U', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W'}, {'F', 'Z', 'W'}, {'Z', 'R', 'W'}, {'Z', 'U', 'W'}, {'Z', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'G', 'W'}, {'R', 'G', 'W'}, {'U', 'G', 'W'}, {'G', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'R', 'W'}, {'F', 'U', 'W'}, {'F', 'W', 'C'}, {'U', 'R', 'W'}, {'R', 'W', 'C'}, {'U', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'U', 'R'}, {'F', 'R', 'C'}, {'F', 'U', 'C'}, {'U', 'R', 'C'}, {'F', 'Z', 'G', 'W'}, {'Z', 'R', 'G', 'W'}, {'Z', 'U', 'G', 'W'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'Z', 'R', 'W'}, {'F', 'Z', 'U', 'W'}, {'F', 'Z', 'W', 'C'}, {'Z', 'U', 'R', 'W'}, {'Z', 'R', 'W', 'C'}, {'Z', 'U', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'R', 'G', 'W'}, {'F', 'U', 'G', 'W'}, {'F', 'G', 'W', 'C'}, {'U', 'R', 'G', 'W'}, {'R', 'G', 'W', 'C'}, {'U', 'G', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'U', 'R', 'W'}, {'F', 'R', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'U', 'W', 'C'}, {'U', 'R', 'W', 'C'}, {'F', 'U', 'R', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'F', 'R'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'F', 'U'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'F', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'R', 'U'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'R', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'U', 'C'}, {'Z', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'U'}, {'Z', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'C'}, {'Z', 'W', 'F', 'U', 'C'}, {'Z', 'W', 'R', 'U', 'C'}, {'G', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'U'}, {'G', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'C'}, {'G', 'W', 'F', 'U', 'C'}, {'G', 'W', 'R', 'U', 'C'}, {'W', 'F', 'R', 'U', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'U'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'F', 'U', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'R', 'U', 'C'}, {'Z', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'U', 'C'}, {'G', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'U', 'C'}, {'Z', 'G', 'W', 'F', 'R', 'U', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, C, N, U, W, G, K, Z, F and directed edges W->G, N->F, W->K, R->U, N->G, U->F, R->N, G->Z, C->Z, R->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22129727", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node K and node N .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, C, N, U, W, G, K, Z, F and directed edges W->G, N->F, W->K, R->U, N->G, U->F, R->N, G->Z, C->Z, R->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22129727", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node U and node Z d-separated by nodeset {'F', 'W', 'C'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes R, C, N, U, W, G, K, Z, F and directed edges W->G, N->F, W->K, R->U, N->G, U->F, R->N, G->Z, C->Z, R->F.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "22129727", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node C and node G?\nA. {'Z', 'W', 'K', 'R', 'U'}\nB. {'Z', 'N'}\nC. {'F', 'Z', 'U', 'N'}\nD. {'U', 'N'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, C, A, F, P, M, Y, I, R and directed edges I->R, Y->R, C->M, J->F, J->Y, J->M, A->I, P->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "79721835", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node I and node F .", "answer": "[set(), {'A'}, {'P'}, {'Y'}, {'J'}, {'M'}, {'C'}, {'P', 'A'}, {'Y', 'A'}, {'A', 'J'}, {'M', 'A'}, {'A', 'C'}, {'R', 'Y'}, {'R', 'J'}, {'P', 'Y'}, {'P', 'J'}, {'M', 'P'}, {'P', 'C'}, {'Y', 'J'}, {'M', 'Y'}, {'Y', 'C'}, {'M', 'J'}, {'J', 'C'}, {'M', 'C'}, {'Y', 'R', 'A'}, {'R', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'P', 'A'}, {'P', 'A', 'J'}, {'M', 'P', 'A'}, {'P', 'A', 'C'}, {'Y', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'M', 'A'}, {'Y', 'A', 'C'}, {'M', 'A', 'J'}, {'C', 'A', 'J'}, {'M', 'A', 'C'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y'}, {'R', 'P', 'J'}, {'R', 'Y', 'J'}, {'R', 'M', 'Y'}, {'R', 'Y', 'C'}, {'R', 'M', 'J'}, {'R', 'J', 'C'}, {'P', 'Y', 'J'}, {'M', 'P', 'Y'}, {'P', 'Y', 'C'}, {'M', 'P', 'J'}, {'P', 'J', 'C'}, {'M', 'P', 'C'}, {'M', 'Y', 'J'}, {'C', 'Y', 'J'}, {'M', 'Y', 'C'}, {'M', 'J', 'C'}, {'Y', 'R', 'P', 'A'}, {'R', 'P', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'R', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'R', 'M', 'A'}, {'Y', 'R', 'A', 'C'}, {'R', 'M', 'A', 'J'}, {'C', 'R', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'P', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'M', 'P', 'A'}, {'Y', 'P', 'A', 'C'}, {'M', 'P', 'A', 'J'}, {'C', 'P', 'A', 'J'}, {'M', 'P', 'A', 'C'}, {'Y', 'M', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'C', 'A', 'J'}, {'Y', 'M', 'A', 'C'}, {'C', 'M', 'A', 'J'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y', 'M'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y', 'C'}, {'R', 'P', 'J', 'M'}, {'R', 'P', 'J', 'C'}, {'R', 'M', 'Y', 'J'}, {'C', 'R', 'Y', 'J'}, {'R', 'M', 'Y', 'C'}, {'R', 'M', 'J', 'C'}, {'M', 'P', 'Y', 'J'}, {'C', 'P', 'Y', 'J'}, {'M', 'P', 'Y', 'C'}, {'M', 'P', 'J', 'C'}, {'C', 'M', 'Y', 'J'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'Y', 'M'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'Y', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'J', 'M'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'J', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'Y', 'J', 'M'}, {'A', 'R', 'Y', 'J', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'Y', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'M'}, {'A', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'C'}, {'A', 'P', 'Y', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'P', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'Y', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'M'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'C'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y', 'M', 'C'}, {'R', 'P', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'R', 'Y', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'P', 'Y', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'M'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'Y', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'Y', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'M', 'C'}, {'A', 'R', 'P', 'Y', 'J', 'M', 'C'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, C, A, F, P, M, Y, I, R and directed edges I->R, Y->R, C->M, J->F, J->Y, J->M, A->I, P->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "79721835", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node I and node F .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, C, A, F, P, M, Y, I, R and directed edges I->R, Y->R, C->M, J->F, J->Y, J->M, A->I, P->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "79721835", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node M and node A d-separated by nodeset {'F', 'R', 'C'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes J, C, A, F, P, M, Y, I, R and directed edges I->R, Y->R, C->M, J->F, J->Y, J->M, A->I, P->I.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "79721835", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node R and node F?\nA. {'I', 'M', 'P', 'A'}\nB. {'I', 'M', 'J'}\nC. {'P', 'A'}\nD. {'M', 'P', 'C'}", "answer": "B", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, F, O, T, R, W, S, P, X and directed edges E->X, S->X, E->F, E->R, O->W, T->X, S->P, O->R, O->P.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "29647717", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node R and node X .", "answer": "[{'E'}, {'S', 'E'}, {'W', 'E'}, {'F', 'E'}, {'E', 'O'}, {'E', 'T'}, {'S', 'W', 'E'}, {'F', 'S', 'E'}, {'S', 'P', 'E'}, {'S', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'E', 'T'}, {'F', 'W', 'E'}, {'W', 'E', 'O'}, {'T', 'W', 'E'}, {'F', 'E', 'O'}, {'F', 'E', 'T'}, {'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'E', 'T', 'O'}, {'F', 'S', 'W', 'E'}, {'S', 'P', 'W', 'E'}, {'S', 'W', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'T', 'W', 'E'}, {'F', 'S', 'P', 'E'}, {'F', 'S', 'E', 'O'}, {'F', 'S', 'E', 'T'}, {'S', 'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'T', 'P', 'E'}, {'S', 'E', 'T', 'O'}, {'F', 'W', 'E', 'O'}, {'F', 'T', 'W', 'E'}, {'P', 'W', 'E', 'O'}, {'T', 'W', 'E', 'O'}, {'F', 'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'F', 'E', 'T', 'O'}, {'T', 'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'W', 'F', 'P', 'E'}, {'S', 'W', 'F', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'W', 'F', 'E', 'T'}, {'S', 'W', 'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'W', 'P', 'E', 'T'}, {'S', 'W', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'S', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'T'}, {'S', 'F', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'S', 'P', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'W', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'W', 'F', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'W', 'P', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'F', 'P', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'S', 'W', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'O'}, {'S', 'W', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'T'}, {'S', 'W', 'F', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'S', 'W', 'P', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'S', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'W', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'O', 'T'}, {'S', 'W', 'F', 'P', 'E', 'O', 'T'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, F, O, T, R, W, S, P, X and directed edges E->X, S->X, E->F, E->R, O->W, T->X, S->P, O->R, O->P.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "29647717", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node R and node X .", "answer": "{'E'}", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, F, O, T, R, W, S, P, X and directed edges E->X, S->X, E->F, E->R, O->W, T->X, S->P, O->R, O->P.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "29647717", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node F and node S d-separated by nodeset {'W', 'X'}?", "answer": "No.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, F, O, T, R, W, S, P, X and directed edges E->X, S->X, E->F, E->R, O->W, T->X, S->P, O->R, O->P.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "29647717", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node E and node O?\nA. {'F', 'R', 'P', 'T'}\nB. {'F', 'R', 'W', 'P'}\nC. {'R', 'W', 'P', 'X'}\nD. {'F', 'T', 'X'}", "answer": "D", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, W, C, G, D, Q, Y, X, V and directed edges W->X, G->X, W->V, D->X, Y->X, L->C, Q->X, W->G, C->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "12300569", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node Q and node C .", "answer": "[set(), {'G'}, {'W'}, {'D'}, {'V'}, {'Y'}, {'L'}, {'G', 'W'}, {'D', 'G'}, {'G', 'V'}, {'G', 'Y'}, {'G', 'L'}, {'D', 'W'}, {'W', 'V'}, {'W', 'Y'}, {'W', 'L'}, {'D', 'V'}, {'D', 'Y'}, {'D', 'L'}, {'V', 'Y'}, {'V', 'L'}, {'Y', 'X'}, {'Y', 'L'}, {'D', 'G', 'W'}, {'G', 'W', 'V'}, {'G', 'W', 'Y'}, {'G', 'W', 'L'}, {'D', 'G', 'V'}, {'D', 'G', 'Y'}, {'D', 'G', 'L'}, {'G', 'V', 'Y'}, {'G', 'V', 'L'}, {'G', 'Y', 'X'}, {'G', 'Y', 'L'}, {'D', 'W', 'V'}, {'D', 'W', 'Y'}, {'D', 'W', 'L'}, {'W', 'Y', 'V'}, {'W', 'L', 'V'}, {'W', 'Y', 'X'}, {'W', 'Y', 'L'}, {'D', 'V', 'Y'}, {'D', 'V', 'L'}, {'D', 'Y', 'X'}, {'D', 'Y', 'L'}, {'V', 'Y', 'X'}, {'V', 'Y', 'L'}, {'Y', 'L', 'X'}, {'D', 'G', 'W', 'V'}, {'D', 'G', 'W', 'Y'}, {'D', 'G', 'W', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'Y', 'V'}, {'G', 'W', 'L', 'V'}, {'G', 'W', 'Y', 'X'}, {'G', 'W', 'Y', 'L'}, {'D', 'G', 'V', 'Y'}, {'D', 'G', 'V', 'L'}, {'D', 'G', 'Y', 'X'}, {'D', 'G', 'Y', 'L'}, {'G', 'V', 'Y', 'X'}, {'G', 'V', 'Y', 'L'}, {'G', 'Y', 'L', 'X'}, {'D', 'W', 'Y', 'V'}, {'D', 'W', 'L', 'V'}, {'D', 'W', 'Y', 'X'}, {'D', 'W', 'Y', 'L'}, {'W', 'Y', 'X', 'V'}, {'W', 'Y', 'L', 'V'}, {'W', 'Y', 'L', 'X'}, {'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X'}, {'D', 'V', 'Y', 'L'}, {'D', 'Y', 'L', 'X'}, {'V', 'Y', 'L', 'X'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'V', 'Y'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'V', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'Y', 'X'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'Y', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'V', 'Y', 'X'}, {'G', 'W', 'V', 'Y', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'G', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X'}, {'G', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'L'}, {'G', 'D', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'G', 'V', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'W', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X'}, {'W', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'L'}, {'W', 'D', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'W', 'V', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'V', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'G', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'W', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}, {'G', 'W', 'D', 'V', 'Y', 'X', 'L'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, W, C, G, D, Q, Y, X, V and directed edges W->X, G->X, W->V, D->X, Y->X, L->C, Q->X, W->G, C->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "12300569", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node Q and node C .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, W, C, G, D, Q, Y, X, V and directed edges W->X, G->X, W->V, D->X, Y->X, L->C, Q->X, W->G, C->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "12300569", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node C and node V d-separated by nodeset {'Q', 'G', 'W', 'D', 'X', 'L'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes L, W, C, G, D, Q, Y, X, V and directed edges W->X, G->X, W->V, D->X, Y->X, L->C, Q->X, W->G, C->Y.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "12300569", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node Q and node L?\nA. set()\nB. {'D', 'G', 'V', 'X'}\nC. {'D', 'G', 'W', 'X'}\nD. {'D', 'G', 'X'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, G, V, D, P, M, W, N, S and directed edges K->M, V->W, P->N, V->S, K->N, V->D, P->W, G->N, D->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38836285", "sid": 0, "question": "Find one valid nodeset that can d-separate node W and node K .", "answer": "[set(), {'S'}, {'G'}, {'D'}, {'V'}, {'P'}, {'M'}, {'S', 'G'}, {'S', 'D'}, {'S', 'V'}, {'S', 'P'}, {'S', 'M'}, {'D', 'G'}, {'G', 'V'}, {'G', 'P'}, {'G', 'M'}, {'D', 'V'}, {'D', 'P'}, {'D', 'M'}, {'P', 'V'}, {'M', 'V'}, {'M', 'P'}, {'P', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'D'}, {'S', 'G', 'V'}, {'S', 'G', 'P'}, {'S', 'G', 'M'}, {'S', 'V', 'D'}, {'S', 'P', 'D'}, {'S', 'M', 'D'}, {'S', 'P', 'V'}, {'S', 'M', 'V'}, {'S', 'M', 'P'}, {'S', 'P', 'N'}, {'D', 'G', 'V'}, {'D', 'G', 'P'}, {'D', 'G', 'M'}, {'G', 'V', 'P'}, {'G', 'V', 'M'}, {'G', 'P', 'M'}, {'G', 'P', 'N'}, {'D', 'P', 'V'}, {'D', 'M', 'V'}, {'D', 'M', 'P'}, {'D', 'P', 'N'}, {'P', 'V', 'M'}, {'P', 'V', 'N'}, {'M', 'P', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'V', 'D'}, {'S', 'G', 'P', 'D'}, {'S', 'G', 'M', 'D'}, {'S', 'G', 'V', 'P'}, {'S', 'G', 'V', 'M'}, {'S', 'G', 'P', 'M'}, {'S', 'G', 'P', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'V', 'D'}, {'S', 'M', 'V', 'D'}, {'S', 'M', 'P', 'D'}, {'S', 'P', 'D', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'V', 'M'}, {'S', 'P', 'V', 'N'}, {'S', 'M', 'P', 'N'}, {'D', 'G', 'V', 'P'}, {'D', 'G', 'V', 'M'}, {'D', 'G', 'P', 'M'}, {'D', 'G', 'P', 'N'}, {'G', 'V', 'P', 'M'}, {'G', 'V', 'P', 'N'}, {'G', 'P', 'N', 'M'}, {'D', 'P', 'V', 'M'}, {'D', 'P', 'V', 'N'}, {'D', 'M', 'P', 'N'}, {'P', 'V', 'N', 'M'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'V', 'P'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'V', 'M'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'P', 'M'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'P', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'V', 'P', 'M'}, {'S', 'G', 'V', 'P', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'P', 'M', 'N'}, {'S', 'D', 'P', 'V', 'M'}, {'S', 'D', 'P', 'V', 'N'}, {'S', 'D', 'P', 'M', 'N'}, {'S', 'P', 'V', 'M', 'N'}, {'G', 'D', 'V', 'P', 'M'}, {'G', 'D', 'V', 'P', 'N'}, {'G', 'D', 'P', 'M', 'N'}, {'G', 'V', 'P', 'M', 'N'}, {'D', 'P', 'V', 'M', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'V', 'P', 'M'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'V', 'P', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'P', 'M', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'V', 'P', 'M', 'N'}, {'S', 'D', 'P', 'V', 'M', 'N'}, {'G', 'D', 'V', 'P', 'M', 'N'}, {'S', 'G', 'D', 'V', 'P', 'M', 'N'}]", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, G, V, D, P, M, W, N, S and directed edges K->M, V->W, P->N, V->S, K->N, V->D, P->W, G->N, D->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38836285", "sid": 1, "question": "Find the minimal nodeset that can d-separate node W and node K .", "answer": "set()", "question_type": "FO", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, G, V, D, P, M, W, N, S and directed edges K->M, V->W, P->N, V->S, K->N, V->D, P->W, G->N, D->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38836285", "sid": 2, "question": "Are node V and node P d-separated by nodeset {'S', 'G', 'M', 'D'}?", "answer": "Yes.", "question_type": "YN", "task_type": "d-separation"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes K, G, V, D, P, M, W, N, S and directed edges K->M, V->W, P->N, V->S, K->N, V->D, P->W, G->N, D->S.", "graph_type": "DAG", "uid": "38836285", "sid": 3, "question": "Which of the following nodesets can d-separate node D and node G?\nA. {'S', 'P', 'W'}\nB. {'M', 'W', 'N'}\nC. {'W', 'K', 'N'}\nD. {'S', 'W', 'N'}", "answer": "A", "question_type": "MC", "task_type": "d-separation"}
